<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CareerPilot</string>
    <string name="nav_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="arts">\nThe Arts stream is an academic pathway that encompasses a diverse range of subjects related to human expression, society, and culture. It is one of the primary streams students can choose after completing their 10th grade. In the Arts stream, students typically engage with subjects such as literature, history, sociology, psychology, economics, and political science. This stream offers a platform for individuals to explore and understand the complexities of human thought, creativity, and societal dynamics.</string>
    <string name="commerce">\nThe Commerce stream offers a broad understanding of commerce</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="arch">Architecture is the art and science of designing and constructing buildings and structures. It combines creativity, technical knowledge, and practical skills to create functional and aesthetically pleasing spaces. Architects play a vital role in shaping our built environment, ensuring that spaces are not only visually appealing but also functional, efficient, and safe for occupants.</string>
    <string name="engineering">Engineering is the application of math and science to design and create solutions for real-world problems, from bridges to microchips. Engineers use creativity and technical skills to innovate and improve the world around us.</string>
    <string name="medical">Medical education encompasses undergraduate studies, medical school, residency training, and ongoing professional development. It prepares individuals for careers as physicians, offering specialized training in various fields of healthcare. After completing medical school and residency, physicians obtain licensure to practice medicine and may pursue further specialization through fellowships or certifications.</string>
    <string name="pcmb_career_options">After completing studies in the PCMB group (Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, and Biology), you have a wide range of career options to consider. Some potential career paths include:</string>
    <string name="pharmacy">After completing a Pharmacy program, you have various career opportunities available. Some potential career paths include:</string>
    <string name="counsellor1">Dalbir has worked with educational institutions for over six years, where she trains students to build their soft skills, public speaking and interview skills,etc.\nShe is also a certified career counsellor who has worked with 100s of students to guide them towards fulfilling paths and enhancing their productivity.</string>
    <string name="counsellor2">Deepa spent 7 years in the corporate sector with compaines like Kotak Life(Mumbai) and Pacer Automation(Bengaluru).\nFor the last 3 years, she has been working closely with school students(Grade 8-12) and College graduates helping them in choosing the right future path for themselves. </string>
    <string name="counsellor3">Shreenath has more than two decades of experience and a multi-disciplinary academic background ranging from Science to Theology, etc. He has led the Union of Evangelical Students of India for over 24 years as State Secretary.</string>
    <string name="counsellor4">Dr Anupama holds a PhD,MPhil,MSc in BioTechnology, and has been teaching at Amity University for 19+ years.Also a co-ordinator for their senior students.</string>
    <string name="bsc_pcm_info">B.Sc. in Physics, Chemistry, and Mathematics is an undergraduate program that offers in-depth knowledge in the fields of physics, chemistry, and mathematics.</string>
    <string name="forensic_science_info">Forensic science involves the application of scientific principles and techniques to investigate crimes and analyze evidence. It encompasses various disciplines such as biology, chemistry, physics, and computer science. Forensic scientists collect, preserve, and analyze physical evidence found at crime scenes, including DNA, fingerprints, fibers, and firearms. They use specialized equipment and methods to uncover information that can be used in criminal investigations and legal proceedings. Forensic science plays a crucial role in the criminal justice system, helping to solve crimes, exonerate the innocent, and ensure justice is served.</string>

</resources>